slax.org 2019-03-25

# Privacy - Slax Linux

Your privacy is important to us. So we've developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions. 

This website strives to offer its users the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party. 

### How we gather information from users

We never collect your personal information while using Slax (the software application). However, we may collect your personal information while visiting our website (slax.org). How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase. Like most Web sites, slax.org also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site, and we may not be able to customize the site's features according to your preferences. 

### What we do with the information we collect

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site, software and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our business partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually. 

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on slax.org to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; services and products offered by us and other topics we think you might find of interest. 

Personally Identifiable Information collected by the website may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of ecommerce transactions, and other communications with you. We will use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases. 

### Changes to this Policy

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site or software following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.
